hi everyone welcome back uh this is my
name is Dyan Grant and this is part four
of my presentation on man life
insurance um yes I just want to um let
you know just so refresher that man life
insurance represents B Mobility um uh
for the the employees for short-term
bability okay man life insurance is
located um in Montreal Quebec okay
Canada man life is all over the place
but the the location that I I dealt with
was located in Montreal Quebec I am in
Ontario
okay damages um man life is responsible
for everything that happened to me
thereafter because they were um um
deceitful yep and as we go along you
will see now I'm at 2018 part one of
three okay thank
you again please feel free to pause and
read if I'm going too fast all right I'm
just trying to summarize don't want to
be too long thank
you 2018 interaction via emails between
Adrian nicolini sib lawyer and my life
insurance also provided information to
Adrian nicolini due to the deception of
man life insurance and B Mobility U man
life insurance placed my job on the line
so I kept um Adrian nicoline informed I
felt comfortable with Adrian nicoline
his involvement right WSB lawyer since
he was able to respond effectively to
man life insurance and the mobilities
lawyer right I did not realize it was
all an act I thought it was genuine okay
so ad nicolini nicolini Law Firm um he
was aibb lawyer um he started to respond
to man life on my behalf in January 2018
okay so
here January 16 2018
um man life had included Adrian nicolini
because he responded to man life okay
and man I I don't really want to read I
don't want to read it's got a lot of the
information here man life um have been
provided us incorrect information okay
it was more in favor of B Mobility so
anything they say it's roally
misconstrued okay Sal and benefits were
orientated in January salary retroactive
I got it retro active back to November
2017 right and I started physiotherapy
on January 10th okay and
here ashleen steel right um based off
what man life request was and all that
ashleen steel on January 17th responded
Ashley steel is um one of uh the
legal um person there at nicolini Law
Firm okay she's one of of nicoline in-
laws
representative okay um so ashleen
responded kindly find attached Dr
silverberg um report Dr silverberg's
report dat in November 17th 2017 just
letting you know again that man life
insurance is has been
um has been um ignoring that's the word
ignoring Dr Silver Bird's report so I
guess the lawyer here recognized is that
based on the information here January 16
that man life um um included
so here was a response and she uh
ashleen steel provided the report again
to man life okay it was attached all
right please be free to pause and read
okay because in this in the meantime
here she was actually defending me okay
I would just read what highlighted in
green Dr silverberg's report is quite
clear that Miss Grant is unable to
return to her pre-disability duties at
this time and then it says in addition
as you will note Dr silverberg's
November 2017 2017 report November 17
2017 report um he indicates that even
with a local cortisone injection she
would not be suitable to return to pre-
disability um duties man life was
so um forceful telling me that I need to
take the cortisone injection they want
to actually damage me if we don't you
see if you don't know you're right if
you don't know yourself and know that
they're telling you to do wrong you will
follow them and then you're are the one
who suffer later on and that's what they
wanted the I didn't the in the cortisone
injection would not have helped me okay
please ref you to pause and read thank
you and I this is my little thing I put
through put um put together about man
life man life insurance violated the can
Canadian Human Rights Act and you can
read if you can and criminal act please
read the deception man life insurance
company continued to so obvious that man
life insurance
involvment influence the medical system
okay please feel free to read this is a
summary of things that man life did so
we know definitely that man life was
either the company's racist or the
company is just does it to
everyone so that a company will not pay
out um to an injured person or whatever
you understand so whatever it is it's
still defying still violating the kenned
and human rights act
okay deception of the fapy clinic
continues 2018 brandton
Physiotherapy and the wellness Institute
CER by man life insurance this start my
clinical notes January 2018 to March
2018 I actually started this brand
physiotherapy clinic in in um on the
23rd of March 2017 as you could see but
um my life did not get the time to dist
start my medical records then instead
they seize my benefits okay so I went by
to the clinic cuz I think the clinic had
everything the clinic had everything
thing exercise um I I was getting
exercise for my hand I was getting uh um
the Des treatment um what they put on my
hand and all that not a not a paper
towel like quality care right this
Clinic was well equipped so I trusted
them Bible say trust no one but I did I
trusted them um in 2017 so I went back
to them in 2018 when I was when I um
benefits was reinstated
okay however I showed you this before
that they distorted when uh money life
now got to them okay money life got to
them there was a planning process so um
they I had a different um
physiotherapist the phist I had in um La
in 2017 march to April 2017 was really
nice and really good you know however I
had this time Rohit Sony and I could
tell something was wrong I could tell I
could I actually felt it I could tell
that um he was deceitful I I could tell
it I could see it in his eyes actually
anyway here it was proof that they this
was transposed right the letters then
when I got um my brace because he was
the one at first recommended that I get
a new brace and that um I need T I need
a t machine to take home so I can use a
t machine at night so he said he's going
to request it I didn't he said he's
going to requested okay um so on
February
21st the um man life sent a brace but it
was a left the left side the left brace
you see it was clear for them e you see
it still could like be a um the r but
you see it bright enough to form the L
as you can see my injuries was right
hand thetis and left hand lateral
and read okay thank
you but a clearer view of the letter
from manone Life Insurance
okay left okay here it is left manock
REO RIS
brace okay please be free to pause and
read thank
you deception of the physiotherapy
Clinic continues there was a plan in
place by man life but brm physiotherapy
did not submit a request for the right
hand new new brace immediately after the
left prce was returned right they said
they were going to do it and I think
something started um in March on March
7th
2018 right but realize that it was
submitted exactly one month later why
did it take so long e March 21st 2018
man Life Insurance Specialist what the
reason man Life Insurance Specialist
I've realized right was the reason for
the delay so as to deny my injury and
benefits okay request of committed again
to man life insurance but with another
transposition of the letters
okay here it is so this was submitted in
January okay this was it and if you
notice the difference okay submitted
March 21st 2018 luckily I I am a person
who love I am keeping records right so I
got this in this this um I asked for a
copy of the um
my report and this is what I got when I
was in when I was at the clinic so right
there the receptionist handed me this so
receive copy of report at clinic in 2018
then for whatever was going on in 2019 I
decided I couldn't find I couldn't find
my copy thank God I couldn't find my
copy cuz I didn't realize that there was
a change again in March it was when I
asked um via email I called actually
called and asked for a copy they said
they will send it via email which I
received a copy via email on February 26
2019 I F I got a copy of the report
again and thank God I found the one that
I got in House at the clinic right and
then I was thinking I let me put aside
but then I recognize something they're
different they are different as you can
see okay trans transposition and intent
to deceive okay please feel feel free to
review thank
you and it continues here it shows that
um it's my right hand okay yet it says
chronic left decra vean this is right
hand they have chronic left decra vean
okay um tenosinovitis since June um 2016
right and then they said here that I
wear a right thumb brace so if it's left
if it if it's left why am I wearing a
right thumb brace okay so as you can see
they are trying to the the the
transposition here new submission March
2018 which is also transposed
okay p is free to pause and
read and here I've already summarized
the same thing so you can pause and read
if you'll wish okay I've already went
I've already gone through uh um I've
already explained actually okay so
please feel free to pause and read okay
you see
this and you see that they are different
okay thank
you money life insurance company request
a description of functional abilities
form to be computed by the office of Dr
James Chang notice I'm telling you they
are ignored they were ignoring Dr
silverberg okay my new specialist was Dr
Sam silverberg Dr James CH insisted that
the functional abilities form should be
completed by the new specialist form was
completed on February 10 2018 by Dr Sam
silverberg I went Dr Sam silverberg
office and they said yes they will
complete it okay and I informed man life
insurance they wouldn't have it oh boy
okay my life insurance was never has had
never asked Dr Sam Anders man when I was
forced back to work to use my left Time
Dr Sam and Dr Sam handles man in in
March and June was never asked for a
functional abilities report never you
understand but decided to distort my
records that's why I was forced back to
work that's why I was denied in November
okay okay um my return to work on March
prior to my return to work on March 15
2017 I was not reassessed on March 7th
2017 but was forced to return to work to
use my left hand man life insurance did
not ask for description of function
abilities report and on June 12th 2017
okay please free to pause and read thank
you
here okay
um it is proof that Manny life had asked
Dr James
Chang to for a report he says on January
2nd I sign provided with a functional
form it's a other form at at the time
for my doctor to complete um functional
form to be compl Ed by your physician
okay all
right I got a
letter from man life insurance I will
address this section at a later date
okay at a later not a later date I
should say at a later time in my
presentation sorry about
that as soon as man life insurance
company realized that I was waiting on
Dr silverberg to complete this descript
functional functional abilities form I
was forced to see The Specialist Dr Aon
Bon on February 21st 2018
okay man life insurance com communicate
with Dr James CH quality Care Dr handers
men bton physiotherapy Clinic what never
once communicat Dr
silverberg and here is Dr silverberg's
report Dr silverberg did write by me Dr
silverberg actually with all the
question and stating here you you see um
do um it says here we noted that
cortisone injection was recommended by
Dr Al Anders man but the patient refused
injection on July 26 2017 you get it you
get it considering she considering the
reoccurring presentation of the symptoms
reoccurring my thing is not was not
reoccurring you see because doctor you
see doct hman gave the impression that I
was better when I was when I went back
to work but they had me using my left
hand then when I went there
in when I went him in June Dr handers
Man actually um did me wrong again so
man life was um this was the plan of man
life anyway right but Dr silverberg said
a patient has a right to refuse any
treatment I suspect that a cortisone
injection will not completely abolish
your pain cortisone injection cortisone
reduces inflammation but does not heal
an injury therefore her response would
be part at best you understand and there
are other information here that um this
Dr silberg defended me based on the
questions asked and then he even even
added here there is no medical treatment
that can heal an injury she injured
herself performing her job and the pain
will increase if she returns to that job
you understand okay be feel free to
pause and read if you
wish and this report was sent on
February 10
18 manual life would hav have it right
threatened by man life insurance to see
they appointed appointed specialist Dr
eron Bon on February 21st 2018 okay
please feele free to pause and read all
right cuz this was after Dr um
silverberg gave facts that report to man
life they decided
yeah threaten that I should see there
especially 21st
okay please to pause and read if you
wish on February 19th here it says
February 19th you know I got the
information
um again actually um Erin Dr eron Bon
autopedic surgeon um and and man life
stated Adele belile honestly Adele
belile I should have ever told you
before yes she bullied me that's why I
didn't really I didn't want to speak um
with my life anymore she bullied me and
shouted and go and went on
yeah however she was being so adamant
that I see this specialist right and she
said please take note that your
short-term disability benefits will be
suspended should you decide not to
attend this appointment or that your
cooperation is not satisfactory for the
report for the expert to proceed with
the evaluation she knew why she said if
I did not cooperate cooperate all right
because it would have been in favor of
man life and not in favor of me cuz
whatever went on I I will continue and
you'll know right
okay I have included Dr silverberg's
report for a reason for reference okay
as you can see on February 10
2018 um Dr silverberg submitted the
description andun abilities form um on
on on my situation right to Money life
insurance money life insurance has been
ignoring Dr
silverberg's report on me right cuz he
had he is a doctor of Integrity now I
was forced to see their doctor Dr Erin
Bon right on February 21st 2018 you know
I was threatened from my previous um
slides that indicated there there's a
letter that that stated that if I didn't
go what would have happened so I went
okay and uh the report came out on
February 28th 2018 and I was a bit
disturbed by the report because there
are so many pages of the report and I'm
thinking what did this doctor do this
doctor did nothing you understand hence
the reason why man life said if I didn't
cooperate I was being asked questions I
sat in the Dr Erin Bon's office
I was seated while she questioned me
with um asking me information asking me
questions that did not have any relation
to my injury but you know what I
cooperated you know I cooperated because
of the threat by man life okay I in my
opinion I felt that I was being
psychoanalyzed I was I sat there for an
hour with all these unrelated questions
okay and then this doctor based of the
information here it says my dis date of
disab disability was October 25th 2017
this wasn't it at all this was my second
time being off however maybe I guess
drct uh um man life gave this doctor um
this date but as you can
see Dr silverberg Who listened to me and
recorded the correct information right
on June he indicated June 2016 this was
the date of my actual injury I was
feeling pain then right and then I was
off work on short-term disability as of
September 7th
2016 right now my injury was over a year
old right and this doctor has uh just um
that's why her report was so biased I
she had so many information as I
realized with the system the system um I
guess with the Dig digitalized system it
can be um uh they can pull your record s
that's why I said my records at Ministry
of Health that's not is incorrect they
can pull your records okay and I guess
that's what she did to have so much
information and then it to what the
information misc conscrew okay please
ref free to pause and read thank
you okay um CH has a past medical
history I I figured with the digitalized
system and all that everything is
brought up you know everything thing you
can see everyone can see your medical
records and all that so she's she was
able to recognize that I'm healthy do
this is 2018 okay all right when um she
said Miss Grant is healthy okay okay
Miss Grant um
um she she had a few information here I
didn't have any other any joint symptoms
I had I any other joint symptoms I she
indicated here I had previous surg yes
for
endometriosis okay and then um some
stuff here I I didn't get I didn't get
Whiplash from the first accident I was
not great I wasn't greatly injured
nothing to really talk about okay and um
She said deny it it means that I was
denied by wsib and here he questions
like uh um high school diploma and she
recorded high school diploma and and
actually she has this section wrong
because I was working towards my CPA yes
okay um some things here um she has an
employment history 19 years okay going
on 20 um then she indicated here that
there are some a symmetry in her distal
forearm and risk which I would attribute
to hand dominance she's actually seeing
that my hand is fat wow anyway wow
disrespect hey disrespect
okay please feel free to pause and read
okay thank
you okay um
so she said here I don't know she she
justes she should just make up her mind
at one point in time it says here right
here she would be capable of returning
to her previous position that's what she
said right my previous position was to
fastpac environment front line right
position however in her notes she also
said providing a position where she did
not have to do much keyboarding if it
were available would be the ideal
situation that's it that I put out here
you understand my hand was still stolen
she said she said that um um she would
believe that my injury would have been I
would have been better because um it
says one however ever would expect this
to be temporary and resolve over
approximately 6 to 12 weeks you
understand my injury was in June and I
worked up until September so it was 12
weeks right and I didn't get care if I
got IM immediate care I would have been
better okay um here um number
three number three it says here I did I
said it did not go away I had not used
my right hand for over a year that when
that when that ultrasound was completed
because she made mention of about um
ultrasound okay I guess this is it here
yes this is the ultrasound information
and it confirmed de of anness and Theus
okay Dr hesman I I already went through
this right this is this is this is proof
Dr Anders man she actually is saying Dr
Anders man I refuse the um cortisone
injection so I am I am bringing it out
here they said I refuse the cortisone
injection okay what did Dr Andis man say
this is it right here right here see it
here if there if there is no
inflammation not warranting an injection
if there I don't have to go further if
there is no information not warranting
an injection okay here it says if if
inflamed inject if there's in if if a
cordone injection is done if there's
inflammation and a cordone injection is
done then what then it say stated what
is next but here we don't have to go any
further okay please rev the view
review if inflamed inject it means that
if there's no inflammation
do not inject but if there is
inflammation inject okay common sense
and I can read and have understanding
all
right the doctor Dr Monique Chris krisar
Chris tarus
right stated by Word of Mouth that Dr
Handelman wanted me right to still get
the injection that day although
there wasn't any fluid it's indicated in
red here okay and then she said I
refused the injection which was not
needed and it says Corone is used as an
inter inter anti-inflammatory medication
right but they were trying to damage me
please feel free to pause and read thank
you here it is no fluid if inflame
inject so if it is not inflamed why ask
me why I offer the injection and then
State I refuse you see the deception and
the medical system working together okay
please ref you to pause and read thank
you and this is my
hand Dr um Erin Bon stated that um my
hand is fat actually H it looks deformed
okay please feele free to pause and read
it's actually I'm actually saying the
same thing I don't have to read it again
okay I just I'm giving a summary
okay Dron reports bias yes okay please
feel free to pause and read I have
highlighted this it said in all
likelihood mingran suffered from right
detis that could possibly be associated
with the change in our position and
change in our workpl in our workstation
one however would expect to be it to be
this to be temporary and resolve over
approximately 6 to 12 weeks yes if they
had um attended to me when I was uh
telling my
supervisor pain in my hand and in July I
told my supervisor my hand is swen and I
was ignored so I was not attended to B
Mobility ignored my Cry for Help
okay and on um March 23rd it says here
um
Adele B says we did not hear back from
you cuz um we have the assessment result
and we'll be able to provide um the
report shortly okay so she got the
report from Dr Arin Bon the bias report
okay please feel free to join me in part
two of 2018 thank
you